Guide to the Pare Lorentz papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Other Films, 1938-1969, undated
  - Subseries 5. Other Films, 1930s-1963
    - The Face of The Earth, 1950-1963
      - The Face of the Earth, 1950-1963 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1951 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - The Land, 1951 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - My Brother’s Keeper, 1949 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 6. John Vachon Stills, 1930s-1940s
    A large collection of still photographs taken by John Vachon, an acclaimed New Deal era shooter. Most of the pictures depict the American Northwest.
    - Still Photos of the Northwest, 1930s-1940s, (26 Folders) (Box 65, Folder 1 to 26)
    - Still Photos of the Northwest, 1930s-1940s, (22 Folders) (Box 66, Folder 1 to 22)
- Series VI: Office Files, 1935-1979, undated
  This series contains Pare Lorentz’s office files, as well as files from organizations and businesses with which he was associated, including RKO Pictures and the Resettlement Administration. These records consist mainly of expense reports and general correspondence. They are arranged alphabetically. The date ranges may not always be exact. They are taken from labels on Lorentz’s file drawers, rather than from the content of individual folders.
  - Subseries 1. RKO Files, 1941-1942, undated
    After Congress ceased funding the U.S. Film Service, Lorentz signed a two-picture deal with RKO. Here is correspondence and files related to that experience.
    - Alphabetical Correspondence, 1941-1942, (37 Folders) (Box 67, Folder 1 to 37)
    - General Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Copyright, 1941-1942 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2. General Office Files, 1936-1941
    These files contain some records from New Deal agencies, including the Resettlement Administration and the Farm Security Administration, as well as personal records from Lorentz’s business transactions.
    - Automobile Expenses, 1937-1938 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Audio Productions Inc., 1937-1938 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Bills of Lading--Incoming, 1936-1937 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Bills of Lading--Outgoing, 1936-1937 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Bills of Lading--Incoming, 1938 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Bills of Lading--Outgoing, 1938 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Bills of Lading--Miscellaneous, 1936-1938 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Boston Water Purifier Co., 1937 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Books, 1936-1938 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Brentanos, 1938 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Bridgeman--Agent-Cashier, 1937- 1938, (2 Folders) (Box 69, Folder 11 to 12)
    - Bridgeman--Travel, 1937-1938, (2 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 1 to 2)
    - FSA Budget, 1938 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Commercial Stationery Co., 1936 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Contracts, 1936-1938, (2 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 5 to 6)
    - De Luxe Laboratories, 1938 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Eastman-Kodak Stores, 1936-1937 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Equitable Stationery Co., 1936-1938 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Twentieth Century Fox, 1937-1938 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Film Library--Museum of Modern Arts, 1937-1938 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Film Receipts, 1937-1938 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - General Service Studios, 1936-1938 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Government Movies, undated (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Goerz-American Optical Co., 1938 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - H.E.R. Laboratories, 1937 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Irving Browning Studios, 1936 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Lorentz--Agent-Cashier, 1936 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Lloyds Film Storage, 1936-1937 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - March of Time, 1937-1938 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Motion Picture Lighting and Equipment, 1937 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Movietonews Inc., 1937-1938 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Music Publishers Protective Association, 1937 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Moss Manufacturing Co., 1938 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Motion Picture Camera Supply, 1936-1937 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - National Screen Service, 1937-1938 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - National Cine Laboratories, 1938 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - New York Telephone Co., 1938 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Office Supplies, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Office Moving, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Office Supplies--Washington Requisitions, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Postal Telegraph, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Pavelle Laboratories, 1937-1938 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Peerless Towel Supply Co., 1938 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Periodicals, 1938 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Paramount East Coast Bills, 1937-1938 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Personal Telegrams, 1937 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Pathe News, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Paramount Distribution--Correspondence, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Paramount West Coast, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Preview Theater, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Railway Express Agency, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - RCA Communications, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Romeike Clippings Service, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Royal Typewriter Co., 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - RCA Manufacturing, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Ruby Camera Co., 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Ralph Steiner, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Stackpole Sons, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Sound Effects, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Still Photos, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Todd and Robertson, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - United Artists Studios, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Willard Van Dyke, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Western Union, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Horace Woodard, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - Stacy Woodard, 1936-1938 (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - Atkins, 1939-1941, (2 Folders) (Box 73, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Associated Film Audiences, 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - "A", 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Applications for Jobs, 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - AAA (Scripts), 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Bridgeman and Miriam Bell, 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - "B", 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - "C" Fight For Life, 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - "C", 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - The City (Scripts), 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - "D" Fight For Life, 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - De Kruif, 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - "D", 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Flaherty, 1939-1941(Agricultural) (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - "F", 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - "G", 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Gercke (AAA), 1939-1941, (2 Folders) (Box 73, Folder 18 to 19)
    - "G" Fight For Life, 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Samuel Goldwyn, 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Mr. Griswold, 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - "H", 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Ivens (REA), 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - J-K, 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - "L", 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Locke, 1939-1941, (2 Folders) (Box 73, Folder 27 to 28)
    - Lorentz (Personal), 1939-1941 (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - Lorentz (Misc), 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - "M", 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - "M" (AAA), 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Mercey, 1939-1941, (2 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 4 to 5)
    - "M" Fight For Life, 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - "N", 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Nosler, 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - "O", 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - "P" Fight For Life, 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - "R", 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - REA, 1939-1941 (Scripts) (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - "S", 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - "S" REA, 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - "S" Fight For Life, 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - "T" Fight For Life, 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - "T", 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - "U", 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - "W", 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - "W", 1939-1941 (REA) (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Atkins, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Baker, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - Bartley, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - Bell, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Beaton, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Berger, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - Brennan, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - Bridgeman, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - Comfort, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 29)
    - Clothier, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 30)
    - Crosby, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 31)
    - Davis, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 32)
    - Davidson, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 33)
    - Dildine, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 34)
    - Doyle, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 35)
    - Frumkin, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 36)
    - Finley, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 37)
    - Geer, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 38)
    - Gercke, 1938-1940 (Box 74, Folder 39)
    - Griswold, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Gray, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Haynes, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Henderson, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Hughes, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Howarth, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Hamilton, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Holcombe, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Holt, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Jahns, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Johnson, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Frank Lee, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Locke, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Lowrance, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Lorentz, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - McCormick, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Martin, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Meyer, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Mooney, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Montgomery, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Noodel, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Nosler, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Pruett, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Pulman, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Polvinale, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Raymond, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Redden, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 27)
    - Roberts, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 28)
    - Smith, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 29)
    - Swenson, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - Service Certificates, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 31)
    - Steinbeck, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 32)
    - Thompson, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 33)
    - Tucker, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 34)
    - Thorne, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 35)
    - Townsend, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 36)
    - Walker, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 37)
    - Wilhoit, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 38)
    - Woit, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 39)
    - Time and Leave Rules, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 40)
    - Individual Travel Reports, 1938-1940 (Box 75, Folder 41 to 46)
    - Individual Travel Reports, 1938-1940, (28 Folders) (Box 76, Folder 1 to 28)
    - Prints--Record, 1938-1940 (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Sales Reports, 1938-1940, (2 Folders) (Box 76, Folder 30 to 31)
    - Sales Reports, 1938-1940, (4 Folders) (Box 77, Folder f.1 to 4)
  - Subseries 3. U.S. Film Service, 1935-1949
    The files from the U.S. Film Service contain office records, as well as correspondence with contributors to the government effort to document American conditions during the Great Depression. U.S. Film Service files are located here, but researchers should note that they are also scattered throughout this series.
    - Footage, 1940-1941 (Box 78, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Financial, 1936-1940 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Budgets, 1937-1940 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Belmont Theater, 1940 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Bonneville, 1940 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Bridgeman, 1938-1939 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Krellberg, 1940-1941 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Lorentz Expenses, 1940 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Financial--Fight REA, 1939 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Applicants--General, 1938-1941, (2 Folders) (Box 79, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Applicants--Technical, 1936-1941 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Film Service Property, 1940-1941 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Department of Commerce, 1937-1940 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Name Files--A-J, 1935-1938, (8 Folders) (Box 80, Folder 3 to 10)
    - Name Files--R-Z, 1935-1938, (6 Folders) (Box 81, Folder 1 to 6)
    - Name Files--A-M, 1936-1938, (33 Folders) (Box 81, Folder 7 to 39)
    - Name Files--M-S, 1936-1938, (7 Folders) (Box 82, Folder 1 to 7)
    - Name Files--B-N, 1936-1940, (8 Folders) (Box 82, Folder 8 to 15)
    - Name Files--M-W, 1936-1940, (12 Folders) (Box 83, Folder 1 to 12)
    - Automobile Research, 1941 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Oliver Griswold, 1938-1941 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Edwin Locke, 1938-1939 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Testimony, 1936-1939 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Stryker Card Files, 1940s (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Budget Presentation to House Committee, 1941 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - American Veterans Committee, 1949 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1943-1948 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1947 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings, 1938-1942 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Distribution, 1938-1939 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Relay Reports, 1940 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1939-1950 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Secretary of the Interior Correspondence, 1942-1946 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 4. Personal Files, 1935-1947
    . This subseries contains clippings, correspondence, and expense reports.
    - American Film Center, 1935-1947 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Associated Realist Films, 1935-1947 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Association of School Film Libraries, 1935-1947 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Authors’ Guild, 1935-1947 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Biographies--Lorentz, 1935-1947 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Invitations--Clubs and Associations, 1935-1947 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Invitations--Lectures, 1935-1947 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Howell, Soskin and Co., 1935-1947 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Judge, 1935-1947 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - King Features, 1935-1947 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - League of American Writers, 1935-1947 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Letters--Introduction, 1935-1947 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - McCall’s--General, 1935-1947 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - McCall’s--Fan Letters, 1935-1947 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - McCall’s--Wiese, Otis, 1935-1947 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - McCall’s--Contracts, 1935-1947 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1935-1947 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Official
      - Department of the Interior, 1935-1947 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - FSA, 1935-1947, (2 Folders) (Box 87, Folder 5 to 6)
      - FWA, 1935-1947 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Nec, 1935-1947 (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - National Defense Council, 1935-1947 (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - RA, 1935-1947 (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - REA, 1935-1947 (Box 87, Folder 11)
      - USFS, 1935-1947 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - The Players, 1935-1947 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Proposed Productions--John L. Sullivan, 1935-1947 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Proposed Productions--John Henry, 1935-1947 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Publicity--Personal, 1935-1947 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Requests--Reprint Rights, 1935-1947 (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Requests--Movie-Making, 1935-1947 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Requests-Writing, 1935-1947 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Screen Directors Guild, 1935-1947 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Stackpole, Sons, 1935-1947 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Hollywood Trip, June-September 1939 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Trips-Key West, 1940 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Trips-London, 1935-1947 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Trips-West Virginia, 1935-1947 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - William Morris Agency, 1935-1947 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - United Nations, 1935-1947 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Camera--Fan Mail, 1935-1947 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Camera--T.J. Maloney, 1935-1947 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Personal Files, A-M, 1935-1947, (25 Folders) (Box 89, Folder 1 to 25)
    - Personal Files, N-Z, 1935-1947, (13 Folders) (Box 90, Folder 1 to 13)
  - Subseries 5. General Files, 1930s-1948
    Most of these records deal with the various federal agencies with which Lorentz collaborated.
    - Dam Photos, 1937-1940 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - TVA Photos, 1937-1940, (2 Folders) (Box 91, Folder 2 to 3)
    - Carded Stills--A Million Men on Wheels, 1937-1940 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1937-1940, (2 Folders) (Box 92, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Bonneville Project, 1937-1940 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Academy Photo Offset, Inc., 1937-1940 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Advance Cine Equipment Co., 1937-1940 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - AAA, 1937-1940, (2 Folders) (Box 92, Folder 6 to 7)
    - Altec Service Corporation, 1937-1940 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Air Travel, 1937-1940 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Amusement Supply Company, Inc., 1937-1940 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Art Metal Construction, 1937-1940 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Appropriations, 1937-1940 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Auto, 1937-1940 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Bids, 1937-1940 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Contract--USFS Movie, 1937-1940, (2 Folders) (Box 93, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Contracts--Gasoline, 1937-1940 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Express, 1937-1940 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Expense Vouchers, 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Procurement, 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Gasoline, 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Shipping Expenses, 1937-1940, (2 Folders) (Box 94, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Telephone and Telegraph, 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Travel, 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Martin’s Files, 1937-1940
      - Equipment Ordered Deluxe, 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Ecce Homo Selected Takes, 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - Production #3--Assembled Film, 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - Production #3--Screenings, 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - Production #3--Key Nos., 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 12)
      - Prints Ordered De Luxe, 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 13)
      - Prints and Equipment In Stock Deluxe, 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 14)
      - Receipts Films, 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 15)
      - Railway Express, 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 16)
      - Shipments--Washington, 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 17)
      - Shipments--Misc., 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 18)
      - Work Orders, 1937-1940 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Academy Awards, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture Department, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - American Documentary Films, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - American Film Center, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - American Magazine, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Amkino Corporation, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Association of Documentary Film Producers, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Associated Press, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Association of School Film Libraries, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Bankhead-Jones Farm Tenant Act, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Bangsbergh, Raymond, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Best Film Company, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Booklets and Releases, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - British Broadcasting Corporation, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - British Documentary Films, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - British-Gaumont Pictures Corp., 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Consolidated Film Industries, Inc., 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Educational Film Institute, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - Educational Information, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - ERPI--Royalty Prices, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - FSA Photographic Lab Price List, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Federal and State Agency Directories, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - Film Daily, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 23)
    - Films Incorporated, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - French Cinema Center, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - Frontier Films, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - Garrison Film Distributors, Inc., 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - Goldwyn Studio West Coast Contract, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 28)
    - Gootrad and Gootrad, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 29)
    - Hollywood Motion Picture Institute, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 30)
    - Housing Authority, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 31)
    - Information Requests, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Interior Department, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - International Cinema Institute, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Jay Emanuel Publications, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Jersey Homesteads, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Labor Unions Government Employees, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - League for American Writers, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Legislation, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Liberty Magazine, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Life, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Look, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - MacFadden Publications, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Maritime Commission, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - March of Time, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - MGM Corp., 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Metropolitan Motion Picture Council, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Motion Picture Producers and Distributors of America, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Modern Talking Picture Service, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Motion Picture Corporations of America, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Motion Picture Daily and Herald, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Movie Information, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Music Recording, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - National Board of Review, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - National Emergency Council, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - National Broadcasting Company, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - New Directions--James Laughlin IV, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 27)
    - New Republic, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 28)
    - New York Post, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 29)
    - New York Times, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 30)
    - Phonograph Records, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - President’s Inaugural Address, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Prisons, Bureau of, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Requests for Advice, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Reorganization Bill Text, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Register and Tribune, Des Moines, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - RKO Radio Pictures, Inc., 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Screen Directors Guild, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Seven Seas Film Corporation, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Skouras Theatres Corp., 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Shock Troops of Disaster, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Social Security Board, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Soil Conservation Service, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Roosevelt Address--"Children in a Democracy," 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Staff Meeting Notes, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - State Department, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Subcommittee Hearings, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Theatre Arts Monthly, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Time, Inc., 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - Treasury Department, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - Treasury, Secretary of, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - Tygart Valley Data, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - United Artists, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 23)
    - Universal Newsreel Company, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 24)
    - United States Film Service, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 25)
    - U.S. Government "Bill of Complaint" Against Movie Producer Monopolies, 1937-1940 (Box 97, Folder 26)
    - U.S. Research Corporation, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Variety, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Visual Education, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Warner Brothers, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Wilding Picture Productions, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Wilson Company, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - YWCA Motion Picture Bureau, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Works Progress Administration, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - World’s Fair, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Travel Advances, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 10)